1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl(appurl)
9. waitForPageLoad(2)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. delay(2)
21. zee5 = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Zee5 image check"), 5)
25. if (zee5 == true)
1. println("Homepage Loaded successfully")
29. delay(5)
33. delay(5)
37. premium = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Premium on homepage"), 2)
41. if (premium == true)
1. println("Premium section is present on Homepage")
45. shows = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Shows on homepage"), 2)
49. if (shows == true)
1. println("Shows section is present on Homepage")
53. movies = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Movies on homepage"), 2)
57. if (movies == true)
1. println("Movies section is present on Homepage")
61. news = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/News on homepage"), 2)
65. if (news == true)
1. println("News section is present on Homepage")
69. videos = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Videos on homepage"), 2)
73. if (videos == true)
1. println("Videos section is present on Homepage")
77. livetv = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/LiveTv on homepage"), 5)
81. if (livetv == true)
2. println("LiveTv section is missing on Homepage")
85. TvGuide = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/TvGuide on homepage"), 5)
89. if (TvGuide == true)
1. println("TvGuide section is present on Homepage")
93. Languageicon = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Language icon on homepage"), 5)
97. if (Languageicon == true)
1. println("Language icon section is present on Homepage")
101. Searchicon = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Search Icon on homepage"), 5)
105. if (Searchicon == true)
1. println("Search Icon section is present on Homepage")
109. Login = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Login in homepage"), 5)
113. if (Login == true)
1. println("Login  section is present on Homepage")
117. Threedotmenu = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Threedot menu on homepage"), 5)
121. if (Threedotmenu == true)
1. println("Threedotmenu  section is present on Homepage")
125. premiumcontentscheck = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Premium contents on Homepage"), 1)
129. if (premiumcontentscheck == true)
1. println("Premium contents are present on Homepage")
133. scrollToElement(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/ContentsPlay on Homepage"), 2)
137. delay(10)
141. click(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/ContentsPlay on Homepage"))
145. delay(30)
149. waitForPageLoad(20)
153. mouseOver(findTestObject("TVShowspageObjects/Menubarwhilecontentplayback"))
157. element = findWebElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/TVShowspageObjects/Pausebuttonwhilecontentplay"), 45)
161. executeJavaScript("arguments[0].click()", Arrays.asList(element))
165. delay(5)
169. navigateToUrl(appurl)
173. waitForPageLoad(5)
177. maximizeWindow()
181. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Zee5 image check"), 5)
185. carousalcheck = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Carousal on Homepage"), 5)
189. if (carousalcheck == true)
1. println("Carousal is present on Homepage")
193. aboutUs = getText(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/AboutUs on Homepage"))
197. println(aboutUs)
201. if (aboutUs.contentEquals("About Us"))
1. println("About Us is present on Homepage footer")
205. contactUs = getText(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Contact Us on Homepage"))
209. println(contactUs)
213. if (contactUs.contentEquals("Contact Us"))
1. println("Contact Us is present on Homepage footer")
217. Help = getText(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Help on Homepage"))
221. println(Help)
225. if (Help.contentEquals("Help"))
1. println("Help is present on Homepage footer")
229. privacypolicy = getText(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/PrivacyPolicy on Homepage"))
233. println(privacypolicy)
237. if (privacypolicy.contentEquals("Privacy Policy"))
1. println("PrivacyPolicy is present on Homepage footer")
241. termsofuse = getText(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/TermsOfuse on Homepage"))
245. println(termsofuse)
249. if (termsofuse.contentEquals("Terms of Use"))
1. println("TermsOfuse is present on Homepage footer")
253. closeBrowser()