1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl(appurl)
9. waitForPageLoad(2)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. delay(2)
21. zee5 = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Zee5 image check"), 5)
25. if (zee5 == true)
1. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
29. delay(5)
33. delay(5)
37. shows = waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("TVShowspageObjects/Shows on homepage"), 5)
41. if (shows == true)
1. log = new com.kms.katalon.core.logging.KeywordLogger()
5. println("Shows section is present on Homepage")
45. click(findTestObject("TVShowspageObjects/Shows on homepage"))
49. driver = getWebDriver()
53. i = driver.findElements(By.xpath("//span[@class="ng-star-inserted"]"))
57. println("Click on view all of episodes")
61. get(1).click()
65. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Zee5 image check"), 10)
69. delay(10)
73. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/TVShowspageObjects/Thumbnailchecks"), 5)
77. println("Thumbnails are present")
81. delay(12)
85. g = xpath("//img[@class="thumbnail-image"]"))[1].click()
89. delay(45)
93. mouseOver(findTestObject("TVShowspageObjects/Menubarwhilecontentplayback"))
97. element = findWebElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/TVShowspageObjects/Pausebuttonwhilecontentplay"), 45)
101. executeJavaScript("arguments[0].click()", Arrays.asList(element))
105. delay(2)
109. text = getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/TVShowspageObjects/TitleofPlayingcontent"))
113. println(text)
117. comment(text)
121. obtainedList = new java.util.ArrayList()
125. mySelector = By.xpath("//div[@class="titleoneepisode ng-star-inserted"]")
129. elementList = driver.findElements(mySelector)
133. for (org.openqa.selenium.WebElement we : elementList)
1. comment(we.getText())
5. obtainedList.add(we.getText())
137. sortedList = new java.util.ArrayList()
141. for (String s : obtainedList)
1. sortedList.add(s)
145. Collections.sort(sortedList)
149. Collections.reverse(sortedList)
153. Assert.assertTrue("titles are in ascending order", sortedList.equals(obtainedList))
157. navigateToUrl(appurl)
161. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("TVShowspageObjects/Shows on homepage"), 10)
165. premiumcontentscheck = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Premium contents on Homepage"), 1)
169. if (premiumcontentscheck == true)
1. println("Premium contents are present on Homepage")
173. closeBrowser()