1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl(appurl)
9. waitForPageLoad(2)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. delay(2)
21. zee5 = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("HomepageObjects/Zee5 image check"), 5)
25. if (zee5 == true)
1. println("Homepage Loaded successfully")
29. delay(5)
33. delay(5)
37. click(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/SelectLoginonHomepage"))
41. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/EnterMobileNumber"), 10)
45. click(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/EnterMobileNumber"))
49. sendKeys(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/EnterMobileNumber"), MobileNumber)
53. click(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/Enterpassword"))
57. sendKeys(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/Enterpassword"), Password)
61. click(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/ClickonLoginButton"))
65. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("LoginpageObjects/LoginValidation"), 10)
69. click(findTestObject("LiveTvObjects/MoreoptionsonHomepage"))
73. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"), 3)
77. click(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"))
81. driver = getWebDriver()
85. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"), 5)
89. g = xpath("//img[@class="thumbnail-image"]"))[1].click()
93. delay(45)
97. mouseOver(findTestObject("TVShowspageObjects/Menubarwhilecontentplayback"))
101. element = findWebElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/TVShowspageObjects/Pausebuttonwhilecontentplay"), 45)
105. executeJavaScript("arguments[0].click()", Arrays.asList(element))
109. delay(2)
113. click(findTestObject("LiveTvObjects/MoreoptionsonHomepage"))
117. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"), 3)
121. click(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"))
125. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"), 5)
129. delay(5)
133. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/OriginalspageObjects/Selectanepisode"), 5)
137. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/OriginalspageObjects/Selectanepisode"))
141. delay(45)
145. mouseOver(findTestObject("TVShowspageObjects/Menubarwhilecontentplayback"))
149. element1 = findWebElement(findTestObject("Object Repository/TVShowspageObjects/Pausebuttonwhilecontentplay"), 45)
153. executeJavaScript("arguments[0].click()", Arrays.asList(element1))
157. delay(2)
161. obtainedList = new java.util.ArrayList()
165. mySelector = By.xpath("//div[@class="titleoneepisode ng-star-inserted"]")
169. elementList = driver.findElements(mySelector)
173. for (org.openqa.selenium.WebElement we : elementList)
1. comment(we.getText())
5. obtainedList.add(we.getText())
177. sortedList = new java.util.ArrayList()
181. for (String s : obtainedList)
1. sortedList.add(s)
185. Collections.sort(sortedList)
189. Assert.assertTrue("titles are in ascending order", sortedList.equals(obtainedList))
193. click(findTestObject("LiveTvObjects/MoreoptionsonHomepage"))
197. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"), 3)
201. click(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"))
205. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("OriginalspageObjects/OriginlslinkonHomepage"), 5)
209. a = xpath("//img[@class='thumbnail-image']")).size()
213. b = xpath("//div[@class='premium-button ng-star-inserted']")).size()
217. if (a == b)
2. comment("All originals contents are not premium")
221. comment("Count of Thumbnails in Originals page are :" + a)
225. if (a != 0)
1. comment("Thumbnails are present in Originals page")
229. closeBrowser()